<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jcgordon10.github.io/btbc-av/blog</id>
    <title>My Site Blog</title>
    <updated>2023-04-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jcgordon10.github.io/btbc-av/blog"/>
    <subtitle>My Site Blog</subtitle>
    <icon>https://jcgordon10.github.io/btbc-av/img/favicon.ico</icon>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome]]></title>
        <id>https://jcgordon10.github.io/btbc-av/blog/welcome</id>
        <link href="https://jcgordon10.github.io/btbc-av/blog/welcome"/>
        <updated>2023-04-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey there AV Team!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hey there AV Team!</p><p>I'm excited to share the new "Docs Center" with you all. The hope is that this is going to be the go-to place for all our guides and instructions on how to run the AV team in support of the church's services and activities.</p><p>We know that our team plays a vital role in enhancing the worship experience for everyone at BTBC. Whether it's making sure people can be heard, that lyrics and notes can be followed, or making live streams available to those who can't join in person, we want to help create an engaging and God directed environment for everyone.</p><p>The Docs Center is going to make everyone's life a lot easier. It's a centralized repository of information that's easy to navigate and search. So, if you need to find out how to do something or just want to refresh your memory, you'll be able to do it quickly and easily.</p><p>I want to make sure the Docs Center is as helpful as possible, so please let me know your thoughts and ideas for improving it. We're all in this together, and we want to make sure we're doing the best we can for our church.</p><p>Thanks for being part of the BTBC AV Team!</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Jackson Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>